The Princess Sapphire
Knight of the Ribbon
♪ Atashi no miru yume himitsu nano ♪
The dreams I see are my secret
♪ Dare ni mo iwanai himitsu nano ♪
I won’t tell anyone—it’s my secret
♪ Akai manto hira hira ♪
A red cape fluttering
♪ Uma o tobasu oujo ♪
Galloping on a horse—the princess
♪ Sore ga atashi ♪
That’s me!
♪ Lula-dula-lula-dula ♪
-
♪ Lulu laa, lulaa ♪
♪ Lula-dula-lula-dula ♪
-
♪ Lulu laa, lulaa ♪
♪ Ribon no kishi wa ♪
The Knight of the Ribbon,
♪ Honto wa hontto wa ♪
Truly, truly,
♪ Atashi nano sa ♪
It’s really me!
Forty-Fourth Episode
The Snow Eagle
The Screaming White Eagle
How about this, Doctor?
Come on, it's your turn. Go ahead!
Doctor, I said it's your turn.
Forgive me. Well, that was a fine move.
Now, how's this?
I see, I see.
Then I'll go like this. How about that, Doctor?
Strange.
What's wrong with the Doctor today?
He's usually so absorbed, but his mind is completely elsewhere.
Doctor!
It was my turn, wasn't it? Let's see...
Doctor,
let's stop playing chess.
Come on,
something's bothering you, isn't it? Tell me what it is.
No, it's really something trivial, but it's bugging me.
Look at the heavy snow outside—that snow is what's worrying me.
According to the records, it's the heaviest snowfall in 100 years.
So what about it?
That is the problem.
Lord Sapphire, after a heavy snow like this,
an ill-omened white eagle is sure to appear.
An ill-omened white eagle?
Indeed. They say when it arrives with the heavy snow
and covers the kingdom with its giant wings, misfortune falls upon the land.
Is that what was bothering you? That's just a superstition.
I am a scholar myself.
I don't fear superstition, but history.
In the past, whenever our kingdom faced invasion, there was always...
Doctor, what was that sound just now?
Lord Sapphire... that bad omen I just spoke of is already...
Lord Sapphire, the ominous white eagle has indeed appeared.
I'm more concerned about last night's sound, Doctor.
Sapphire!
Come on down!
Let's build a snowman and play!
Hang on! I'm coming!
Pat-pat-pat...
Sapphire look, it's done!
How is it? Pretty good, right?
It's so-so. But what is it supposed to be?
Ahem! The champion of justice, Ribbon Knight!
That's mean, Sapphire!
You're the mean one, Tink!
The Ribbon Knight is much more slender and stylish than that!
Haha, you fell down!
Hey!
It's Franz!
Did you say Franz?
Hey!
Hello! Welcome!
It's been a while since we had nice weather.
Hello, Tink!
Hello, Franz!
So, what were you making? Come on, let me join in!
Is it that one?
It's me! That snowman is me!
Can you tell?
Of course. It's very well made.
Where's yours? You don't have one.
I know, I'll make one of you!
I'd better take the hint and leave them be.
Wow, it's so pretty.
It feels like I'm back in Heaven.
It's like standing in a huge field of white flowers.
I'm sure I heard something...
Mister, pull yourself together! Come on, mister, speak to me!
He's coming around.
Are you from Silverland?
Take me to the castle.
X is coming. X-Union, with a terrifying weapon.
Yours turned out better after all.
No, Franz, yours is...
Look at that!
Sapphire, I didn't just come over to play.
I was worried about this strange noise...
Could it be...
Sapphire! This is terrible!
It's terrible! X-Union has reached the Orange Forest!
They have some kind of terrifying, unknown weapon!
The border guard has been wiped out!
- What?!
Sapphire, this sound could be X's new weapon.
I'm going to scout the Orange Forest right away.
Care to join?
Tink, lead the way!
Wait for me, Sapphire!
Tink, are you sure it's around here?
No doubt about it, it's definitely around here.
But there isn't a soul in sight.
Franz, don't you feel like someone is watching us?
Now that you mention it, there is a strange presence...
Watch out!
Who's there? Show yourself!
We are X's scouts!
You shall not pass!
Get them!
Sapphire!
Franz!
Take that!
Nice one, Tink!
X!
Retreat!
They're getting away!
You'll regret this day!
I'll give you a real treat. Just sit tight and wait!
Sapphire, this is a bit strange...
Sapphire!
Franz! Over here!
Are you hurt?
I'm fine!
Get down!
An eagle!
That ominous eagle just screeched!
That's ridiculous! Come on!
Wait, Franz! We're coming too!
Prepare to fire!
Fire!
Silverland's castle walls are like scrap paper!
Move out!
Don't falter! We will crush Silverland in one fell swoop!
So that was what caused the scream.
If a giant cannon like that crosses the border, we'll be in serious trouble.
We have to stop them somehow.
That's right, we must stop them ourselves, no matter what!
Sapphire, do you have a plan?
Look over there!
Let's bring down the bridge over that border river!
Look!
The side with the border guard armory wasn't destroyed!
There must be gunpowder there!
Right!
We'll use that gunpowder to blow up the bridge!
What if there are X-Union lookouts at the fort?
Then we'll just drive them off!
Now!
Watch out!
W-W-Wait a second...
Whew, thank goodness...
Tink, I took care of them!
Give me a hand!
Okay!
All right! With this much gunpowder, we can blast them with the cannon!
The problem is how to carry all this gunpowder to the bridge.
Hey, I have a great idea!
We can make a pulley and transport it with that.
Speed up!
Giddyup!
Yahoo!
Wheee! Yahoo!
Careful, Tink! Keep jumping around like that and you'll fall off!
Charge!
Oh, it's X!
W-what?
There they are!
Sapphire, watch out! The edges of their skis are blades!
What!?
Oh no!
What's wrong, Sapphire?
The reins have been cut! I can't steer the sled!
I hear Sapphire's voice. Sapphire!
Franz!
Sapphire!
We're going to crash into the bridge!
Tink, are you alright?
Yeah, I'm managing.
Tink!
Sapphire, these guys were guarding the bridge!
Sapphire!
Yes!
The gunpowder fell right into the river! There's nothing we can do! Let's fall back to the fort for now!
The fort...
has fallen!
If we go in there, we'll suffer the same fate!
Giddyup!
Fire!
The ravine! If we can make it to that ravine...!
I thought it felt hot—my glove is scorched!
That surface acts just like a lens!
A lens? This is it!
If we use this...
this ravine is narrow and prone to avalanches!
If we can blow up that huge cannon...
The sun is directly overhead, too!
This just might work!
Everyone, split up and hurry! Find the biggest piece of ice you can!
Okay!
If we don't hurry, the cannon will pass through the ravine!
With all this snow, you'd think there'd be ice everywhere,
but when you actually need it...
I can't find any!
What does Sapphire want with ice anyway?
I'm on top of the ice! No, no, no! I'm gonna fall!
Found it! I found it!
Sapphire, aren't you done yet? My hands are freezing!
Just a little more, hang in there!
Sapphire, what are you going to do by carving ice?
A lens! I'm making a giant lens!
Watch out!
This ravine is prone to avalanches!
If you fire by mistake, we'll all be wiped out!
Listen up!
No matter what happens, under no circumstances are you to fire!
I see! I get it now!
So you're planning to blow up that cannon with this lens?
Exactly! And luckily, look at the sun!
It's on our side!
Shine on, sun! Celebrate X-Union's conquest of Silverland!
Behold this power!
This mighty strength!
X-Union shall become the rulers of the world!
Damn it! We missed!
Franz! Hurry! Aim for the fuse!
The enemy is up there! Archers! Archers!
Franz! Watch out! Franz, be careful!
I'm fine, I'm fine! You be careful too!
Oh, just you wait!
Fire! Fire!
The light's reaching the fuse...!
Wh-who did that?! Help!
Tink! Hold on tight!
Sapphire! Don't let go! Hang on!
Franz!
Sapphire!
I'm glad you're okay.. Are you hurt?
Thank you!
By the way, what happened to the cannon? Let's go take a look..
We did it!
The X army is completely wiped out!
The cannon is buried under the snow!
The wounded white eagle vanishes in the power of the sun.
But there is no telling when
the X-Union will attack again.
We must defeat them with our own strength..
No matter what, I must protect this peace...
♪ Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa ♪
-
♪ Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo! ♪
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
♪ Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa ♪
-
♪ Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo! ♪
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
♪ Sen'nen man'nen hyakuman-nen ♪
A thousand years, ten thousand years, a million years,
♪ Ribbon de tsunagou ichioku-nen ♪
Let’s connect with ribbons for a billion years!
♪ Akuma ga kute mo arashi ga kute mo ♪
Even if demons come, even if storms arrive,
♪ tsunaida kokoro wa hanarenai ♪
Our bonded hearts will never part.
♪ Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa ♪
-
♪ Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo! ♪
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
♪ Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa ♪
-
♪ Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo! ♪
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Subtitled by
SilverlandSubs
tinyurl.com/SilverlandSubs
Opening & Ending Song Lyrics Translation by
Natalia Arlovskaya
lyricstranslate.com/en/
translator/natalia-arlovskaya
EAN-13 : 8-031179-423880
ASIN : ‎ B0DQ54LVY1
EAN-13 : 8-031179-426225
ASIN : ‎ B0F1V5YTQP